# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

#### IMMACULATE WANGARI OMONDI

### P.O BOX 3207-40100 KISUMU, KENYA

**MOBILE NUMBER: +254741559636** 

EMAIL: wangariimmaculate21@gmail.com

### PERSONAL DETAILS

Year/Date of Birth : 20<sup>th</sup> November 2001

Sex : Female

Nationality : Kenyan

Language : Kiswahili and English

Marital status : Single

ID Number : 39780421

Religion : Christian

## **PROFILE**

Highly motivated, conscientious, and competent collaborator who possess in depth knowledge and expertise within this industry. Maintaining high standards, and assisting my employer in achieving their commercial objectives. With a desire and passion for continuous professional development. I am confident I can add value to your organization by always ensuring your customers and clients receive the best service possible.

## **CAREER OBJECTIVES**

To work at a dynamic organization that will fully utilize the skills and experience acquired to foster my professionalism and career advancement while developing and advancing the organization.

# **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

Sep 2023-current Work at JOOTRH, IT department

June 2022- November 2022: Assistant clerk at Bungoma Law Court

## EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

2019 to current : Kenya College of Accountancy University (KCA

University)

Diploma in Business Information Technology

February 2015- November 2018: Mbale Shalom Girls' High School

Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education (KCSE)

January 2004-November 2014 : Vihiga Education City

Kenya Certificate of Primary Education

### PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES

• A fast learner with a proven track record of achievement

- Proficient in the use of all Microsoft Office Applications and a typing speed of 57wpm.
- Leadership skills, as I have served as a prefect and school president in both primary and high school.
- Exceptional communication skills
- A strong sense of business acumen and understanding that the organizations commercial objectives are crucial to my work
- An adaptable approach to change and someone who can take responsibility for their ongoing professional development.

#### **REFEREES**

1. Mr. George Opano

Jaramogi Oginga Odinga Hospital

ICT In charge

0798045521

2. Mr. Reuben Musanga

Bungoma Law Courts

Court Assistant

0727028276

reuben.musanga@court.go.ke

3. Mr. Brian Mwelusi Mwange

Mbale Shalom Girls' High School

Dean of Studies

0706665544/0790590090